Despite being enemies, I admire your bravery and skill in battle.
即便是敵人 仍不得不佩服你們驍勇善戰
But you should realize by now
然而此刻應該明白了吧
that you will never be able to defeat me.
你們終究敵不過眼前的對手
The human realm will fall under the rule of us demons.
人界將歸我等魔之眷屬的統治之下
Damn it. Is this all that we can do?
可惡 這是我們的極限了嗎
We must not give up, Fred.
千萬不能放棄 弗雷德
In the end, let me send you off myself.
最後由朕親手送你們上路吧
Protection!
防禦晶罩
Ridiculous!
可笑至極
Leo,
雷奧
hang in there.
咬牙撐下去
Yuria!
尤莉亞
Strike Edge!
閃衝爆擊
Charge!
上啊
Hero Max.
勇者麥克斯啊
I am impressed you managed to beat me.
真虧你有本事擊敗本魔王
But unfortunately,
只可惜…
we demons possess seven lives.
我等魔之眷屬擁有七條命
I will resurrect.
朕將會復活
And when I do, I'll make you pay in blood.
屆時讓你們嘗嘗血債血還的滋味
You should be looking forward to it.
好好期待吧
And now,
然後在此時
I've finally
朕終於…
resurrected.
成功復活了
The detestable hero, Max,
可恨的勇者麥克斯
prepare your neck for my vengeance.
給朕洗乾淨脖子等著吧
Congratulations on your resurrection, Your Majesty.
陛下 恭喜您復活了
Long time no see, Zenia.
好久不見 潔妮亞
Are you the only one awake?
只有妳醒著嗎
Where are the others?
其他人呢
The others have not awakened since their battle with the hero ten years ago.
自從十年前與勇者交戰後 至今尚未甦醒
These guys are all the same. Geez.
每個傢伙都一個樣 真拿他們沒轍
By the way, have you grown taller?
話說回來 妳是不是長高了
Please put on some clothes first, Your Majesty.
陛下 您還是先穿件衣服吧
Zenia,
潔妮亞
didn't I ask you to bring my favorite clothes?
不是叫妳拿朕最中意的衣服出來嗎
This is indeed the outfit you loved to wear ten years ago.
那件確實是您十年前愛穿的服裝
But this is what you look like now.
而這是您現在的容貌
It appears that ten years is insufficient
只有十年果然不夠
for you to amass sufficient magical power.
魔力累積不足
Your physical growth is also not complete.
肉體尚未發育完全
And as you can see, some important part of your body…
您的…局部也如您所見
My muscular body is gone.
朕的肌肉都沒了
Please rest assured, Your Majesty.
但是請您放心 陛下
As your secretary, I was prepared for this situation.
我潔妮亞身為秘書官 早已料到這種狀況
I have prepared a few outfits for you.
準備了幾件適合現今陛下的衣服
Zenia,
潔妮亞
what are these clothes?
這是什麼衣服
This is the traditional attire of the sorcerers in human realm.
是人界的傳統魔導士服裝
It's perfect for you.
非常適合您
I have never seen the hero's companions wearing such airy clothing.
朕沒看過勇者的夥伴 穿這種輕飄飄的衣服
This is a maid's uniform known as the "maid outfit."
那是名為"員工服"的侍女工作服
Why do I have to dress like a maid?
為何朕非得打扮成侍女的樣子
This is what you wear to study,
這是學習時穿的衣服
and it has been widely used for many years.
長年以來廣為使用
That's ridiculous.
太瞎了吧
Your Majesty,
陛下
nobody has used that phrase in ten years.
十年前已經沒有人會講 "太瞎了吧"這種用語
LOYALTY AND RIGHTEOUSNESS This one is for water activities…
而這件是需要在水中活動時…
DEMON LORD
(魔王)
Enough!
夠了
Geez. You only bring me weird clothes.
真是的 只會拿怪衣服給朕
I'm terribly sorry.
萬分抱歉
That's not your fault since your usual clothes are also strangely awful.
沒辦法 妳平常的穿著也很怪 不堪入目
What are you talking about, scoundrel?
你這混帳說什麼
Speaking of that, Zenia,
話說回來 潔妮亞
how's that man doing now?
那小子現在過得怎麼樣
Who do you mean by "that man"?
"那小子"是指誰呢
Of course, I am referring to the hero I despised the most, Max.
當然是指朕恨之入骨的勇者麥克斯
After all, that man had the power to defeat me.
畢竟那男人的實力足以擊敗朕
He must have become even better over the past ten years.
這十年來想必變得更加優秀
It is not surprising if he is become a royal.
即使被拜為王族也不奇怪
Tell me, Zenia. How is he doing now?
說啊 潔妮亞 到底是如何
Um… to tell you the truth… actually…
這…不瞞您說…其實…
It is unclear
關於勇者的現況
what the hero's current situation is…
仍是謎團重重…
What?
什麼
At least, he has not made any public appearance in politics or society.
至少沒有在政界 或社交場所拋頭露面
Why? It's baffling.
為什麼 真是令人費解
Ah, I get it.
對了 朕想到了
He must have been isolated from the rest of the world, practicing day and night.
他肯定是遠離俗世 日夜修行
With a humble and sincere mindset, he strives to save all sentient beings.
為拯救眾生而謙虛樸實的心態
He is indeed a true hero.
他果然是真正的勇者
I am looking forward to our reunion more and more.
朕越來越期待跟他重逢了
This way, Your Majesty.
這邊請 陛下
During your slumber, a lot of paperwork has accumulated.
在您沉睡的期間 要處理的公務堆積如山
Please forget about the hero for now.
現在請先忘了勇者吧
How can I do that, Zenia?
那怎麼行 潔妮亞
The hero is our greatest enemy.
勇者可是我等魔之眷屬最大的仇敵
We cannot ignore him.
豈能置之不理
Please forgive my candor.
恕屬下直言
Even if the hero's strength exceeds that of ordinary people,
即使實力超越常人
he is still just an ordinary human.
勇者終究只是普通的人類
He will soon age and die.
立刻就會衰老死去
Your Majesty, there is no need to obsess over such a person.
事已至此 陛下不必執著於那種人
Are you hiding something from me?
妳是不是對朕有所隱瞞
Is there something about the hero that you can't tell me?
關於勇者 有什麼事不能讓朕知道嗎
H-H-How dare I hide something from Your Majesty…
怎…怎麼敢對陛下有所隱瞞…
Could it be that
難道說
the hero has already died?
勇者該不會已經死了吧
Did he die of illness? Or was he assassinated?
病死了 還是被暗殺
Please tell me this isn't true.
拜託 告訴朕這不是真的
Your Majesty, please calm down.
陛下 請冷靜…
I am going to confirm it right now.
朕現在就去確認
The Third Eye!
第三隻眼
This must be the life fluctuation of the stinky hero.
這個毫無疑問是臭勇者的生命波動
Geez. He is clearly still alive.
什麼嘛 明明還活著
Good grief. I got my hope up for a moment.
真是的 害朕期待了一下
DARK CONTINENT, DEMON LORD'S CASTLE
(瓦格納可聯邦 暗黑大陸 魔王城)
He seems to be located near the royal capital of the human realm.
(貝斯卡王國 剛瑪共和國) 看來位於人類王都的附近
I see.
原來如此…
Okay.
好
I will go and come back quickly.
那麼朕去去就回
Where are you going, Your Majesty? Please don't!
您要去哪裡 陛下 千萬不可以
I'm just going to say hello today.
朕今天只是去打聲招呼
I will be right back, so you go make dinner.
馬上回來 妳備好晚餐等著吧
Your Majesty, please stay. The hero is now…
陛下 請您留步 勇者現在…
That's right.
沒錯
The hero must now be at peace.
勇者現在想必是在 歌頌片刻的和平吧
I want to declare my resurrection by taking advantage of this opportunity.
朕要趁機現身宣告復活
I'll remind him of the taste of terror and despair.
讓他回想起恐怖與絕望的滋味
Please do not do that. You will be sorry.
請您打消念頭 不然會後悔的
Enough of that.
少囉嗦…
I woke up early for this very reason.
朕正是為此提早醒來
I will not yield on this point.
這點朕絕不讓步
Please wait, Your Majesty.
請等一下 陛下
His Majesty is so excited.
居然如此興高采烈
Please forgive me for not being able to stop you, Your Majesty.
請原諒我沒能攔下您 陛下
I haven't been to the human realm in a long time.
許久沒來人界
I'm almost there.
就在眼前了
These shabby houses where you foolish people live.
你們這群愚民居住的破爛房子
I see. Civilization is indeed more advanced than that in my memory.
原來如此 文明確實比記憶中更進步
I'm getting closer.
越來越近了
What will the hero's expression be like
當勇者親眼看到朕復活的模樣
when he sees me resurrected with his own eyes?
究竟會露出什麼表情
I can't wait to see that.
簡直等不及了
Is it that building?
就是那棟建築嗎
Excuse me.
打擾了
Long time no see, Hero Max.
好久不見 勇者麥克斯
Open your eyes wide and see. As promised, I have finally resurrected.
睜大眼睛看好 按照約定 朕終於復活了
What's wrong with you? Too scared to speak?
怎麼啦 嚇破膽 發不出聲音了嗎
(Level 1 Demon Lord and One Room Hero)
《Lv1魔王與獨居廢勇者》
(Episode 1: Resurrection of the Demon Lord!)
(#1 魔王復活!)
Who are you?
你誰啊
I'm sorry. It seems I got the wrong place.
不好意思 朕好像找錯地方了
I am Max.
我就是麥克斯
Don't joke with me.
您別說笑了
The third eye and the horn… Are you a member of a demon clan?
頭上的第三隻眼和角…你是魔族嗎
What's the deal with the demon clan coming to me at this point?
事到如今 魔族來找我有何貴幹
This is the Holy Sword Blaze Bringer.
是聖劍烈焰使者
There's no mistake.
絕對錯不了
It was with this sword that you slashed my right shoulder.
你就是用這把劍狠狠砍了朕的右肩
Could it be that you're…
你該不會是…
Oh, you said you would resurrect or something.
對了 你好像說會復活還怎樣
Don't treat the holy sword like trash and throw it around.
不准把聖劍像垃圾一樣亂丟
Sit properly, you little rascal.
臭小子 給朕坐好
You were the hero Max back then? Is this true?
你真的是當時的勇者麥克斯本人 沒錯吧
Didn't I say it already? My back hurts…
我不是說過了嗎 腰好痛
Your body and mind are completely relaxed.
身心都太鬆懈了
Your chin is almost gone.
連下巴都快要不見了
Stop nagging. This is a normal part of the aging process.
吵死了 這是年紀增長的自然變化
You have changed so much in ten years that you are almost a different person.
跟十年前差太多了吧 根本判若兩人
You have no right to criticize me. Why are you wearing a sailor's uniform?
你沒資格說我好嗎 為什麼穿著水手服
By the way, your room is too dirty.
話說回來 房間太髒了吧
And there's an odd smell. Is it the smell of your room?
還有一股異味 是生活臭味嗎
Enough, don't keep smelling.
快停止 不要聞個不停
Is this a container for food?
這是裝食物的容器嗎
This must be discarded immediately or bugs will appear.
要馬上丟掉 不然會招蟲
There are so many tissues. I cannot stand it. I'll help you clean up.
衛生紙也是 受不了耶 朕來幫你整理
You have the nerve to pick up someone else's tissues from the floor.
你居然敢撿 別人家地板上的衛生紙
What is this?
這是什麼
There's a hole in it, and it's very elastic.
開了一個洞 而且彈力十足
Stop, don't touch my things.
住手 不要隨便亂碰
Is this the device used by humans to look for information?
這就是人類使用的情報裝置嗎
I told you not to touch my things.
就叫你不要隨便亂碰了
I can enter text here.
在這裡輸入文字
I see. This can be used to gather information.
原來如此 可以用來調查情報
Humans really have their ways, don't they?
人類還挺有一套的嘛
After all, why are you here?
你到底是來幹嘛的
I almost forgot.
差點忘了
Hero Max,
勇者麥克斯
your fangs have fallen out after ten years of peace, haven't they?
這十年來你沉溺於和平的日子 獠牙都掉光了吧
I hereby announce that I have completely resurrected.
朕在此宣布 已徹底復活
This time, I will unquestionably dominate all of you weak humans.
這一次絕對會完全支配 你們這些軟弱的人類
Can't you show me some reactions?
你不能做點反應嗎
Your archrival is back. You can shout "Do not even think you will succeed!"
宿敵都復活了 可以大喊"休想得逞"之類的啊
There's no need.
不用吧
Are you kidding me?
開什麼玩笑
I woke up early to see your regretful face before your death.
朕可是想趕在你衰老死亡之前 讓你後悔莫及才特地早起的
This has nothing to do with me.
這又不關我的事
You were full of vitality ten years ago.
十年前的你明明充滿了活力
What happened in these past ten years?
這十年來到底發生什麼事
You want to know what happened?
你問我發生什麼事
It's simple.
這很簡單
Nobody needed me after I defeated you and drove away the demon clan.
我打敗你 擊退魔族後 就沒有人需要我了
I lost my foothold without a decent medal and ended up in such a predicament.
連正式勛章都沒有 被逼得無立足之地 淪為這種下場
This is outrageous! Humans are unforgivable.
豈有此理 人類簡直不可原諒
What have they turned the hero who saved mankind into?
到底把拯救人界的勇者 當成什麼了
A hero is a useless burden in a peaceful world.
在和平的世界裡 勇者只是派不上用場的累贅
It can be said that it is a bothersome presence.
反而是礙事的存在
But now it's so relaxing…
不如說現在這樣更輕鬆
Searching for "Hero Max."
"勇者 麥克斯" 搜尋
There's quite a lot. Let me take a look.
跑出不少東西呢 來看一下
Don't look!
不准看
HERO MAX SUSPECTED OF STEPPING INTO OTHER'S MARRIAGE SENT TO PROSECUTORS FOR INVESTIGATION AFTER ASSAULTING A CIVILIAN
(勇者麥克斯 疑似婚外情)
Stepping into other's marriage…
疑似婚外情…
It's not true! I didn't do that.
不是 我沒做那種事
The press conference video is still available.
記者會的影片還留著
Were you thinking with your lower half?
請問你是用下半身思考嗎
You were sweating. You definitely did it, right?
看你冷汗直流 絕對是偷情了吧
I didn't! Listen to my explanation.
才怪 你聽我解釋
I didn't even know she was married.
我根本不知道她結婚了
I was framed!
我是被陷害的
She was a gold-digging hero hunter,
她是盯上錢財的勇者獵人
and her husband was definitely in it too.
絕對跟她老公是一夥的
It's your own fault.
是你自作自受
You got caught because you like having fun and do not take relationships seriously.
誰叫你不是真心的 還動不動對女生出手 才會中計
What's this article about?
下面這篇文章是什麼
What is it?
這是什麼
Assaulting a civilian?
對普通人施暴
Really? You…
你這傢伙是認真的嗎
I didn't do that!
才沒有
That article made it seem like I was the only bad guy.
那篇寫得好像只有我是壞人一樣
It was clear that six thugs suddenly attacked me.
明明是六個小混混突然朝我動手
Of course, I had to fight back when something like that happened.
碰上這種事我當然會抵抗啊
You should have been able to escape easily in such cases.
這種程度而已 你應該能輕易逃走吧
Ten years ago, didn't you just escape from the clutches of my undead legion?
十年前你不就逃過了 朕的不死軍團嗎
But we both got injured that time.
不 那次雙方也不是毫髮無傷啊
You must have become irritable because of drinking.
八成是喝了酒就變得血氣方剛吧
You're so stupid.
真是太蠢了
It's getting more and more interesting. What else is there?
總覺得越看越有趣 還有什麼
Enough, stop looking.
已經夠了吧 別再看了
HERO MAX IS GOING ON DATES WITH TEN GIRLS AT THE SAME TIME What?
(勇者麥克斯 腳踏十條船) 什麼
You've actually fallen to such a low point.
你居然墮落到這種地步
I didn't! Only this article has no facts or evidence to back it up.
才沒有 唯獨這篇是無憑無據亂寫的
I don't remember raising such a bad child like you.
朕可不記得養過你這種壞孩子
What nonsense are you talking about? Calm down, idiot.
說什麼鬼話 冷靜點 笨蛋
I've denied it countless times. I don't know any of those ten girls.
那十個人我一個都不認識 我也否認了無數次
Yet they mocked me as the "Explosive Holy Sword of the Night"
還被揶揄是"夜晚聖劍大爆發"
and "My Holy Sword Blaze Bringer is invincible and sharp to the max."
"我的聖劍烈焰使者無敵鋒利MAX"
Y-Your Holy Sword Blaze Bringer…
你…你的聖劍烈焰使者…
Well… didn't that improve your nighttime reputation?
還挺會講的啊
Shut up!
煩不煩啊
EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEW WITH HERO MAX AFTER HE DEFEATED THE DEMON LORD Do not be so depressed.
(魔王討伐後 勇者直擊專訪) 好啦好啦 你別沮喪
I'll find some of your cool moments.
來找找看你帥氣的一面吧
It's true that I defeated the Demon Lord,
確實是我擊敗了魔王
but it wasn't all on my own.
但絕非憑我一己之力
I was able to face the Demon Lord
正因擁有無可取代的夥伴們
with "the pride of a human being"
以及全世界人民的支持
because of my irreplaceable companions
我才能抱著"身為人類的驕傲"
and the support of people all over the world.
前往挑戰魔王
For me, defeating the Demon Lord was an unavoidable process.
對我而言 這次討伐魔王只是一個必經過程
What can I, as a hero, do now to help preserve this priceless peace?
為了維持這份寶貴的和平 身為勇者 現在能做出什麼貢獻
I believe my future mission is to always seek answers.
我認為不斷探索答案 正是我今後的使命
THE END
(完)
It's so stupid. You seem a bit too full of yourself, don't you?
簡直蠢死了 未免太得意忘形了吧
-Everyone has a hero in their hearts… -I'm laughing so hard that it hurts my stomach…
-人人心中都有一位勇者… -笑得肚子好痛…
Shut up! Stop looking at it!
停下來 別再看了
Your attitude was so arrogant. No wonder some people wanted to expose your secrets.
態度這麼跩 難怪會被揭露糗事
This is what they call "The bigger the tree, the more wind it catches."
這就是所謂的樹大招風
Go tell the "Max" from ten years ago.
麻煩你去跟十年前的我說
And this is what you've become?
結果淪為這副德性嗎
Isn't this a photo of your companions?
這不是你夥伴的照片嗎
You appear to have preserved this photo even better than the Holy Sword.
看來保存得比聖劍好
That's not true.
沒有那回事
The toned physique.
緊實的肉體
The direct gaze brimming with potential.
蘊含潛力的直率眼神
Where did the "Max" from back then go?
當時的你到底消失到哪裡去了
Your obsession with me is kind of creepy.
你對我的執著有點恐怖
How are you getting along with your companions?
跟夥伴之間相處得還好嗎
We haven't seen each other for several years.
已經好幾年沒見面了
The hero is so lonely.
還真是寂寞
It's always been like this.
本來就是這樣
Interests are required for the maintenance of so-called interpersonal relationships.
所謂的人際關係 少了利益就持續不下去
What is the point of those guys meeting me now if there are no benefits?
那些傢伙和現在的我見面 又有什麼好處可言
You're wrong.
你錯了
Your companions have left you precisely
正因為你是那種利己主義的思維
because of your selfish thinking.
夥伴才會離你遠去
You're so annoying. Shut up.
吵死了 閉嘴
Don't act like you know everything.
別說得一副你什麼都懂似的
Get lost. You're an eyesore.
滾回去 你很礙事
Now I understand why Zenia tried to stop me.
終於明白潔妮亞為何攔阻朕
There is no hero here anymore.
這個地方已經沒有勇者了
I'm leaving. We probably won't see each other again.
朕走了 以後再也不會見面了吧
Get lost.
快回去…
By the way,
不過話說回來
since the hero has fallen, humanity has no hope.
既然勇者墮落成這樣 那人界也沒救了
I will wake everyone up immediately when I return. I need to reunite the army.
回去之後立刻把大家敲醒 重組軍隊
We'll see, humans.
走著瞧吧 人類
I agree. It's better to just let this world be destroyed.
贊成 這種世界乾脆毀滅算了
But your companions are a bit in the way.
但是你的夥伴有點礙事
Why don't I attack them now?
不妨現在就去偷襲他們吧
That's a good idea.
這主意不錯
I borrowed money from Leo.
而且我跟雷奧借了錢
As long as he dies, I don't have to pay it back.
只要他死了 我就不用還了
You! Go to
你這傢伙 現在就…
hell, right now!
下地獄去吧
It seems that your skills haven't regressed.
看來…身手沒有退步
Fool.
蠢貨
You wouldn't be able to defeat those people right now.
那些人哪會敗在現在的你手上
I clearly…
朕明明…
Is this a closet?
這裡是壁櫥嗎
The hero didn't give me a fatal blow.
勇者那傢伙 沒有給朕致命一擊
Okay.
好
Hey you.
你啊
Can't you just bear with it for a while while I'm still around?
至少朕還在的時候 不能先忍著別做那檔事嗎
Any objections? Just go to sleep.
搞什麼 你滾去睡啦
Why didn't you kill me?
為什麼不殺了朕
You could've done it if you wanted to.
只要你想要就辦得到吧
I'm not a hero anymore.
我已經不是勇者了
There's no point in defeating the Demon Lord.
打倒魔王也沒有意義
And if I were to defeat you now, the next headline would probably be
而且要是我打倒現在的你
"Hero Abuses and Causes the Death of His Illegitimate Child."
搞不好就會傳出"勇者 虐死私生子"
That would be too much.
這還真過分
Have a cup of coffee.
喝吧 是咖啡
It's bitter. Don't you have orange juice?
好苦 沒有柳橙汁嗎
It's a waste to make coffee for you.
沖咖啡給你真不值得
You're definitely a hero, no doubt about it.
你果然毫無疑問是勇者
Why are you suddenly saying this?
幹嘛突然說這個
Agile moves, excellent skills.
敏捷的身姿 精湛的技術
Your skills haven't declined at all.
絲毫沒有退步
I really felt the hero's burning soul in your heart.
朕確實感受到了 在你心底熊熊燃燒的勇者之魂
Say whatever you want.
那種事隨便你怎麼說
To be honest, you're the one who has regressed.
要說的話 你才退步了吧
You are attempting to attack Leo and the others at this level? What a joke.
只有這種程度還想偷襲雷奧他們 太搞笑了吧
Shut up. I just woke up and haven't gotten into the groove yet.
吵死了 只是剛起床沒進入狀況
Look. Even though my body is in this state now,
看好了 雖然現在身體是這副德性
I'll definitely make a comeback, and take the human realm into my hands.
但朕一定會東山再起 將人界納入手中
When the time comes, you'll have to fight me again.
屆時你也要與朕再次交戰
I'm sorry, but I can't promise you that.
抱歉 但我不能答應你
As you said,
就像你說的
my current situation is all my own doing.
我現在的下場全是我自作自受
But
但是…
I'm truly fed up with this world.
我果然還是徹底討厭了這個世界
I really can't muster the energy to be a hero again.
實在提不起勁當勇者
And heroes are supposed to be born of the times.
而且勇者應該是時代孕育出來的
As long as you cause trouble,
只要你惹事
a new hero will definitely appear.
肯定又會冒出新的勇者吧
Is that so?
這樣子啊
I got it.
朕明白了
Sorry to bother you, and thank you for your hospitality.
打擾了 謝謝招待
Goodbye.
再見
Talking to you is a nice change of mood.
也算是幫我轉換心情了
Bye.
拜拜
I'll take a bath.
去洗個澡吧
I'm back.
朕回來了
Lend me your kitchen.
借一下廚房
Fortunately, I have money from the human realm with me.
幸好我身上帶著人界的錢
People even praised me, saying, "How kind of you to help with grocery shopping."
還被誇獎 "出來幫家裡買菜 真懂事"
You're probably malnourished.
你應該吃得不夠營養吧
I'll cook hot pot for you.
朕煮火鍋給你吃
Wh-What are you doing?
你…你在做什麼
You're scarier now than ten years ago.
現在的你比十年前恐怖多了
Actually, after that, I thought about it too.
其實啊 朕也考慮過了
It would be such a waste to leave a man like you alone.
放著你這樣的男人不管 果然太可惜了
And human society has evolved. I still have a lot to learn.
而且人類社會換了個面貌 朕有好多事要學習
So I will be staying here for a while.
所以朕要暫時借住你家了
Are you kidding me? I can't take care of you.
開什麼玩笑 我哪有辦法照顧你
Take care of me? Don't get it twisted.
哪有辦法照顧朕 別搞錯
I mean, I'll take care of you.
朕的意思是由朕來照顧你
You should be grateful.
好好感謝朕吧
How is it? The hot pot is delicious, right?
如何 很好吃吧
How should I put it? It is indeed delicious.
怎麼說 味道挺順口的
After all, I'm familiar with the five major seasonings in cooking.
畢竟朕熟知料理五大調味料嘛
I'll master your stomach before mastering the human realm.
掌握人界之前 就先掌握你的胃吧
From now on, I'll cook for you every day. Be prepared for that.
以後朕會天天做飯給你吃 做好覺悟吧
It looks delicious.
好像很好吃
Did you just say anything?
你剛才有說話嗎
No.
沒啊
Is that so? Then, let's eat.
是嗎 那就開動吧